<resources>
    <string name="app_name">App1</string>
    <string name="title_home">Vaccines</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Vaccine near me</string>
    <string name="displayimage">displayImage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fullscreen">FullscreenActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="covaxin">COVAXIN</string>
    <string name="info_covaxin">Covaxin (codenamed as BBV152) is an inactivated virus-based COVID-19 vaccine developed by Bharat Biotech in collaboration with the Indian Council of Medical Research - National Institute of Virology.</string>
    <string name="game_over">Game Over</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try Again?</string>
    <string name="position">Position</string>
    <string name="select_an_avatar">Select an Avatar</string>
    <string name="android_trivia">Android Trivia</string>
    <string name="about_text">App1 is a app made to remove all the misconceptions and fears regarding the approved Covid-19 vaccines 💉. App1 help you pick and choose the vaccine which might be best option for you. It also helps you know about the side affects of vaccines and maintains utmost transparency with you 😊.</string>
    <string name="rules_text">Select the answer from the options given. Each time you get an answer correct, you advance to the next question.\n\nIf you get the answer wrong, your game ends! You can return to the title screen using up or back from within the game screen, and this will also end your game.</string>
    <string name="rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="aboutApp">About App</string>
    <string name="trivia_hint">Trivia Hint</string>
    <string name="title_android_trivia_question">Android Trivia (%1$d/%2$d)</string>
    <string name="title_about_trivia">About Trivia</string>
    <string name="title_trivia_rules">Trivia Rules</string>
    <string name="submit_button">Submit</string>
    <string name="congratulations">Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="sharing_not_available">Sharing Not Available</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="titlescreentext">Ready ? Press play</string>
    <string name="exitText">EXIT</string>
    <string name="bio">Hi , 👋.We are fox#01 and we make apps that strive to change the world and touch peoples heart.  We are a team of curious , exquisite and integrous developers. We would like to thank you 🙏 for downloading our app and your feedback would be much appreciated. For feedback or any ideas you would like us to implement contact us at : </string>
    <string name="mohit_email">aswanim96@gmial.com</string>
    <string name="akshat_email">akshat69@gmial.com</string>
    <string name="AboutText">About</string>
    <string name="AboutMeText">About Me</string>
    <string name="lindkin1"><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohit-aswani-345ab31bb/">Mohit Aswani</a></string>
    <string name="lindkin2"><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohit-aswani-345ab31bb/">Akshat Saxena</a></string>
    <string name="side_effects_covaxin">Some mild symptoms AEFIs may occur like injection site pain, headache, fatigue, fever, body ache, abdominal pain, nausea and vomiting, dizziness-giddiness, tremor, sweating, cold, cough and injection site swelling. No other vaccine-related serious adverse effects have been reported.</string>
    <string name="adverse_effect">In case of minor adverse effects such as injection site pain, tenderness, malaise, pyrexia, etc., paracetamol may be used to alleviate the symptoms.</string>
</resources>